Brown, Fred R.; Papers mss004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs and Maps, 1888-1966; 18
  - Photograph: Charles and Hester Brown (Fred's children), Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 50)
  - Album of photographs, ca. 1920s (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 51)
  - Photographs: Charles and Hester Brown, 1929 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 52)
  - Photographs: Elbert Humphrey and Bess Humphrey Hargrove, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 53)
  - Photographs and clippings of other missionaries, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 54)
  - Photographs: Chinkiang, 1927 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 55)
  - Photographs: Amoy, 1930 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 56)
  - Photographs and postcards: Japan, Undated (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 57)
  - Photograph: Fred R. Brown's class reunion, 1935 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 58)
  - Photographs: Water of Life Hospital, Kiukiang, 1949-1950 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 59)
  - Photographs: St James Methodist Church, Cohoes, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 60)
  - Photographs: Clarksville Methodist Church, 1966 (Box 7 (18-Photographs and Maps), Folder 61)
- Miscellaneous, 1916-1918; Undated; 19
  - Slides in metal box, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 1)
  - Bible. Chinese New Testament, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 2)
  - Baby Book, Fred R. Brown, Jr., 1916 (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 3)
  - Baby Book, Hester C. Brown, 1918 (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 4)
  - Travel Brochure, Japan, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 5)
  - "Post Album", Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 6)
    Containing captions (photos have been removed - see Box 7 folder list).
  - Christmas Cards, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 7)
  - Glass slides of church repair and summer house in Kuting, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 8)
  - Lists of lantern slides and negatives, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous), Folder 9)
  - xxx. Unsorted photographs and slides, Undated (Box 8 (19-Miscellaneous))